(忆往昔)
你们对我们造不成威胁
You can't stop any of us.
我们有不死之身  你们这群傻帽
We can't be killed, you stupid little chewtoys.
那些家伙比你们狡猾多了
These things are smarter than you.
你们根本不知道怎么杀它们
You don't have a clue how to kill 'em
或是拖延时间  而你们的计划是什么
Or slow 'em down, and your plan is, what?
正面交锋吗
Go right at 'em?
我们忙着呢
We've been a little busy.
忙着猎杀利维坦
Hunting Leviathan.
太多了  你们见过那个迪克(混蛋)了吗
You met that Dick yet?
我宁愿在垃圾堆里打滚
I'd sooner swim through hot garbage
也不要和你这种下贱的怪物握手言和
than shake hands with a bottom-feeding mutation like you.
我永远不会跟你合作  克劳力
I'd never work with you, Crowley.
我讨厌那帮王八蛋  把他们都灭了吧
I hate the bastard. Squash 'em all.
你们得去见一个名叫弗兰克·德弗罗的家伙
You need to see a fella named Frank Devereaux.
是鲍比·辛格派我们来的
Bobby Singer sent us.
当我没说
Or not. Who?
只需要你帮我们远离牢房
We just need you to get us further off the grid,
同时又能自由行动
but keep us on the board.
清除以前所有的化名
Wipe all your old aliases.
要非常频繁  而且不定期地
Change your phones on a very frequent
换手机  明白吗
non-schedule schedule, you understand?
你不能就这么看着我
You can't just look me in the face
对我说你没事
and tell me you're fine.
-你想听实话吗  -对
- You want me to be honest? - Yeah.
我不想对你撒谎
I don't like lying to you.
感觉不对劲
You know, it doesn't feel right.
所以你猜对了  我最近是很焦虑
So, yeah, you got me there. I been climbing walls.
这个我有体会
I know how that is.
(如今)
(新泽西州  州沃顿森林  松林泥炭地)
晚安  亲爱的
Good night, sweetie.
这是由自然之声出品的
This is Nature Sounds'
《自然之声》第四辑"舒缓的海洋之声"
"Sounds of Nature," Volume 4, "Soothing Seas."
搞毛啊
What the hell?
琳妮
Leanne!
走开
Stay away.
琳妮
Leanne!
这是由自然之声出品的《自然之声》
This is Nature Sounds' "Sounds of Nature.
[邪恶力量 第7季第9集]
(新泽西州  哈蒙顿)
你把电线剥好吗
Did you strip enough wire?
剥好了
Yes, I stripped enough wire.
好了
All right.
看  我就说可以吧
See? Told you.
真惬意
Well, isn't this cozy?
是啊
Yeah.
六号旅馆晚上不给留灯了
Well, Motel 6 just ain't leaving the light on anymore.
这一点上我要谨遵
Well, I'm taking a page out of
弗兰克·德弗罗的圣经指引
Frank Devereaux's Bible on this.
大家都想抓你们的时候
Everybody's out to get you --
疑心病就是情理之中
Paranoia is just plain common sense.
这种日子我们过了好几周了
Weeks, guys. Weeks.
只能洗冷水澡
We've been living with cold showers,
吃凉饭  没有一样是热的
cold hot pockets, cold freaking everything.
我们从没这么落魄过
I mean, this is the bottom that we're living in.
你们知道吧
You guys get that, right?
外面不知有多少像切特那样的大嘴怪
How many big mouths are out there,
在追查我们的信用卡记录
running card traces, like Chet,
或是用别的方法追杀我们
or hunting us down god knows what ways?
现在这个时候
No, now's not the time
我们不能出去抛头露面
to be laying our bed rolls out on the grid.
除非万不得已
Not if we can help it.
屋漏偏逢连夜雨
That's just great.
真是蠢到家了
This is stupid.
咱们的生活质量低到了极点
Our quality of life is crap.
到处是炼狱都受不了的怪物
We got purgatory's least wanted everywhere,
咱们还要为"天下大乱"操心
and we're on our third "the world's screwed" issue
三年之内这是第三次了吧
in, what, three years?
我们开着这辆破车从悬崖边上回来有两次了吧
We've steered the bus away from the cliff twice already.
总得有人出手
Someone's got to do it.
万一这辆车就想开下悬崖呢
What if the bus wants to go over the cliff?
你觉得世界想要毁灭吗
You think the world wants to end?
我觉得要不是咱们每年
I think that if we didn't take its belt
横拦竖挡
and all its pens away each year
这个世界早就自行了断了
that, yeah, the whole enchilada would have offed itself already.
胳膊扭不过大腿的  孩子
Stop trying to wrestle with the big picture, son.
到头来只会伤到自己
You're gonna hurt your head.
你有什么消息
So, what's the guff?
最近在南部松林泥炭地
Well, uh, there have been a rash of sightings
有不少人目击到了
all over the southern pine barrens --
一种移动迅速的类人生物
a strange, fast-moving, human-like creature.
当地人甚至给它起了个名字
Locals even have a name for it.
泽西魔
The Jersey Devil?
我还以为那只是当地人瞎编的故事
I thought that was just local tall-tale crap.
最早在两百年前
The area's history of sightings
就有人见过这种怪物
goes back more than two centuries.
有人说它长着蝙蝠翅膀  还有人说它长着角
Some accounts gave it bat wings, others horns,
还有尾巴
a tail.
还有
And...
对了  还有马头
Oh, yeah, a horse's head.
看草图倒像是楚巴卡(星球大战人物)的头
The sketch looks more like a Chewbacca head.
看来只是搞错了
Sounds kind of mixed-up.
是啊  应该让它和日本机器人过过招
Yeah, kind of like it should be fighting a Japanese robot.
不管是不是搞错了
Well, mixed-up or not,
它貌似刚刚杀了个人
it sounds like it might just have a body count.
"惊现人肉煎饼  露营热季降温"
"Camping High Season Harshed by Human Burrito"?
没错  有家伙把一个露营者挂到树上
Yeah. Something hung a camper up in a tree,
隔着睡袋把他给生吃活剥了
then ate him alive right through his sleeping bag.
他的妻子也失踪了
His wife hasn't been seen, either.
另外  这三周以来
Plus, there have been four other missing persons
还另有四人被报下落不明
reported in the last three weeks.
据州警察称  这是野熊所为
State troopers -- get this -- are saying it's a rogue bear.
可不是嘛  你什么时候见过
Yeah, of course, when was the last time
野熊把猎物吊在树上的
you saw a bear string up its own praeda?
树林里肯定有怪物
Something's out there in the woods.
我们正好可以趁机会去树林里打个猎
Hey, we're going honest to goodness wilderness hunting.
我好久没动双管猎枪了
I haven't used my .30-30 in a while.
好了  大英雄
Okay, Davey Crockett,
游猎还是等到明天
well, safari's gonna have to wait till tomorrow
我们做完调查再说吧
and after our suit-and-tie dance.
我们要先确定这不是某个退隐山林的
We'll make sure this is not just some backwoods crackhead
傻缺豪华露营者干的
who likes to roll glampers.
什么叫豪华露营者
What the hell's a glamper?
萨姆解释一下
Sam?
他们配有高端设备
High-end camper.
电视  交流电  无线网
TV, A.C., Wi-Fi.
回归自然  各种便捷
Back to nature, zero inconvenience.
真傻缺
That's idiotic.
是啊
Yeah.
某些人就是不懂得享受生活
Some people just don't know how to live.
(比格森餐厅)
(限时供应  火鸭鸡三明治)
埃文斯护林员
So, Ranger Evans --
叫我里克就行
Oh, uh, you can call me Rick.
里克护林员
Ranger Rick.
是你发现了米切尔·雷伯恩  对吧
Uh, you were the one who found Mitchell Rayburn, correct?
没错  那个人肉煎饼
The human burrito.
州警察将此案认定为野熊袭击
State police have it down as a bear attack.
是啊  我读了州警察的报告
Yeah, I read what the state police says.
那可不是棕熊干的
That was no rogue brown.
显然  还有其他人报告说看到了
Apparently, some others reported seeing something
更加诡异的生物
a little, you know, weirder.
我做了12年的护林员
You know, I've been a ranger for 12 years.
跟你说句实话
Tell you the truth,
我们不知道哪儿究竟有啥
We have no idea what's out there.
那儿很大  很多树啊什么的
Big. Lot of trees and whatnot.
不过我跟你们说
Tell you this, though.
要对大自然抱有敬畏之心
You got to respect mother nature.
不然的话  她就把你吊起来
You respect her, or she's gonna string you up,
撕开睡袋把你啃个干净
and she'll eat your ass right through the gore-tex.
这么说你认为是大自然干的
So you're thinking it's mother nature?
是这样  我和菲尔这几周
See, me and Phil, we've been finding, uh,
不知是什么东西吃剩的残渣
something's leftovers for weeks --
鹿的残骸  獾子
Deer remains, badger,
别人丢的宠物
missing pets.
菲尔是谁
Who's Phil?
护林队队长助理
Assistant Chief Ranger.
说到这个
Come to think of it,
我有好几天没见着菲尔了
I haven't seen Phil in a couple of days.
不管他在哪个驻地  也该打个电话过来
He's supposed to call from whatever station he's checking off.
你是不是怀疑
But you think maybe
这位护林队队长助理失踪了
your assistant Chief Ranger might be missing?
我也许该做个报告
I should probably report that.
失陪了
Oh. Excuse us.
那么你就
Well, you, uh...
慢慢吃吧
enjoy your lunch...
里克护林员
Ranger Rick.
怎么样
So?
我检查了一下尸体...
Well, I took a look at the cadaver --
残余的部分
what's left of it.
太惨了点
Not a happy camper.
不清楚泽西魔的风格
Don't have any stats on a Jersey Devil,
但从尸体上的啃咬半径来看
but the bite radius on the vic's wounds --
比利维坦的小多了
it's too small for a Leviathan.
而且还留下了心房什么的
And he's still got a ventricle and some change,
所以我想不是狼人干的
so I doubt we're talking werewolf.
食人魔吃东西不剩饭
And a Wendigo don't leave no scraps.
吃午饭吗
Lunch?
饿死了
Starving.
嘿  布兰登
Hey! Uh, Brandon.
有座位吗
We grab a booth?
嘿  孬货  女服务员会招呼你们
Hey, uh, douchewad, a hostess will seat you.
你觉得我他妈像个女服务员吗
Do I look like a freaking hostess?
你希望自个儿像女服务员吗
Do you want to look like a hostess?
你刚才的话不怎么说得通啊
That didn't really make sense, what you... said.
什么意思嘛
What was that?
希望不要在布兰登的地盘用餐
I sure hope we don't get Brandon's section.
大呆鸟要的响尾蛇汤和沙拉组合
Sidewinder soup and salad combo goes to big bird.
肯娃娃(男孩玩偶)要的火鸭鸡三明治
TDK slammer to ken doll.
还有怪叔叔要的小份健康餐
And a little heart-smart for creepy uncle.
你生谁的气呢
What is your problem?
生你的气
You are my problem!
布兰登一股脑把火气全发出来了
Oh, Brandon's got his flare all up in a bunch.
没错  小费是别想要了
Yeah. There goes his 18%.
总之呢  那个护林队队长
Anyway, the Chief Ranger --
我认为他压根不信泽西魔
I don't think he believes in the Jersey Devil.
说到这个  你有没有觉得他像是嗑大了
Oh, by the way, did he seem a little, uh, stoned to you?
你说里克护林员  是啊
Ranger Rick? Yeah.
肯定找了片荒地种了一片大麻
Definitely growing his own on the back 40
把拿来挣钱的那份都抽掉了
and smoking all the profits.
看来他确实认为那里有什么东西
He did seem to think that there was something --
这三明治太好吃了
Oh, that is good sandwich.
你点的是什么
What the hell did you get?
新辣味火鸭鸡三明治
New pepperjack turducken slammer --
限时供应
limited time only.
各种家禽的肉胡乱塞在一起
Bunch of birds shoved up inside each other.
拿造物主开涮呢
Shouldn't play god like that.
你还好意思诋毁我的食物
Hey, don't look at me sideways from that --
你这个古怪的中国鸡肉沙拉又算啥
that chinese chicken geezer salad there, okay?
我这个可好吃了
This is awesome.
是最好吃的三种家禽肉的完美组合
Like the perfect storm of your top-three edible birds.
行了  不管怎样
All right, anyways, um...
那个护林员确实认为
The Ranger did seem to think
沃顿森林里确实有什么东西
there was something out in Wharton forest.
看来是时候去打猎了
Well, then I'd say it's safari time.
你看看她  难道你不认为她很胖
Look at her! You're telling me she's not fat?
行了  去你妈的  迈克
No, no. Up yours, Mike.
去你妈逼
Shove it right up yours!
管他呢  还是吃我的好东西吧
Well, anyway, back to bigger and better things.
几头鹿
Couple of bucks.
大概是为了争地盘顶着脑袋打了一架
Head-butting over turf probably.
赢的肯定是另外一头
Pretty sure the other fella won.
我都忘了
I guess I forgot.
你在成为猎魔人之前  是一个猎人
Before you were a hunter, you were actually a...hunter.
没错  我小时候靠打猎填饱肚子
Yeah, well, we shot our dinner when I was a kid.
你以前常带我们打猎  记得吗
You used to take us hunting. Remember?
爸爸有活儿干  就把我们丢给你照看
Dad had a case, he'd just dump us on you.
见鬼  我们所知的大多数
Shoot, you must have taught us
野外追踪技能都应该是你教的
most of the outdoor tracking we know.
是啊  能教进去多少算多少吧
Yeah, what I could get to stick.
让你们两个小家伙
I never could get you little grubs
朝一头鹿扣动扳机都做不到
to pull a trigger on a single deer.
你是说小鹿斑比吧
Talking about Bambi, man.
怎么能杀斑比呢  傻子
You don't shoot Bambi, jackass.
要杀的是斑比它妈
You shoot Bambi's mother.
看来我们找到菲尔了
Well, looks like we found phil.
特工们
Special agents.
听着  我接到电话了
Listen, I got your call.
但我不太清楚你们说的是什么
But I'm not sure I got what you were saying.
嘿  看来我们找到菲尔了
Hey. I think we found phil.
我就是这么说的
That's what I said.
也许我应该向上头汇报
Uh, I should probably call this in.
没错  这样最好  里克
Yeah, yeah. Solid move, Rick.
这是埃文斯护林员在阿切尔区域汇报  请讲
Uh, this is Ranger Evans up at Acher's point. Come in.
重复一遍  我是护林队队长埃文斯
Uh, repeat. This is Chief Ranger Evans.
我在阿切尔区域发现了情况
I have a situation out at Acher's point.
护林员  有什么东西过来了
Ranger, I think we've got company.
是吗  什么啊
Yeah? Who's that?
护林员
Ranger!
埃文斯护林员
Ranger Evans!
护林员
Ranger!
把他带到树上去了
It's got him up in the trees.
-关灯  -什么
- Lights off. - What?
等等  鲍比  这样真的好吗
Wait, bobby, you think that's really a good idea?
闭嘴  关灯  注意听
Shut up, shut off, and listen.
那家伙在吃里克
Damn thing is eating Rick.
该死  我还喜欢里克呢
Man, I liked rick.
好枪法  鲍比
Wow. Nice shot, bobby.
毫无疑问
Seriously.
各有各的能耐
We all got our gifts.
里克护林员的残骸呢
What about the rest of Ranger Rick?
护林员报告了他的位置  会有人找到他的
Ranger called in his 10-20. His own will find him.
我们还有事要忙
We got crap to do.
这家伙看起来很苗条  可力气真是大
Built like a supermodel, but the thing was strong.
这一点毫无疑问
That's for damn sure.
瞬间就能扛着一个成年人爬到树上
Carried a full-grown man up a tree in nothing flat.
可只用一颗子弹就搞定它了
But it only took one bullet to bring it down.
而且不是银子弹  只是普通的子弹
And not even a silver bullet, just a bullet-bullet.
那颗子弹只是震晕了它
First one must have just stunned it.
行了  我们在它的肥裤里找找身份证
All right, well, let's check its hulk pants for some I.D.
哎呀  都有点腐蚀到皮革了
Oh, that is just gonna ruin the leather.
你没事吧
Are you feeling okay?
我感觉很好啊
Yeah, I feel great.
杰拉德·勃劳德
Gerald Browder,
本镇居民  身高一米七七  褐发蓝眼
uh, lived here in town, 5'9", brown hair and blue eyes...
213斤
235 pounds.
很显然  他减掉了一点赘肉
Well, apparently, he's lost a little pudge.
可能是腹腔带的副作用
Maybe it's a-a lap-band side effect.
什么鬼东西
What the hell?
我想我们最好把杰拉德解剖开一探究竟
I think we better have a look under Gerald's hood.
天啊
God!
它的脏器全泡在这东西里
Its organs are swimming in the stuff.
你们饿不饿
You guys getting hungry?
我饿了
I'm hungry.
那是什么
What's that?
他的胃
His stomach.
作为一个在节食的人
For a guy on a diet,
杰里倒是没少吃啊
Gerry here packed it in pretty good.
那是人肉啊
That's human right there.
那是里克新鲜的肉
That's fresh Rick.
让我再看看
Let's see.
还有...
Plus...
松塔吗
pine cone?
还有一条没拆封的口香糖
Pack of gum in the wrapper.
这个...这个时间长些
That's -- that's older.
也许是菲尔护林员或是那个宿营者
Maybe like a -- maybe Ranger Phil or the camper.
那是什么
What's that?
看起来像...
Looks like a --
对  这是一个猫头
Yeah, that's a -- that's a cat's head.
吃一两个宿营者是一回事
A glamper or two is one thing,
但肯定是饿得不行了才会吃一个猫头
but you got to be damn hungry to eat a cat's head.
看看这啊
Well, look it here.
我不是奥兹医生(健康类电视节目)  但...
I'm no Dr. Oz, but...
我想这是他的肾上腺
I think that's his adrenal glands.
好的  然后呢
Okay. And?
应该是跟旅馆肥皂一样大啊
Meant to be the size of hotel bar soap...
而且是亮橘色
and bright orange.
好吧  这似乎能解释他巨大的力量
All right, that might help explain the strength.
但不管它是什么  总之不是泽西魔
Um, but whatever this thing is, it's not the Jersey Devil,
但它肯定也不再是杰拉德·勃劳德
but it sure as hell ain't Gerald Browder anymore.
好了  伙计们  说真的
Okay, guys, seriously.
可以吃晚饭了吗
It's time for dinner?
杰拉德·勃劳德  35岁  个体户
Gerald Browder, 35, self-employed,
空调修理工
air-conditioning repairman,
是第三个失踪人员
missing person number three,
八天前失踪
disappeared eight days ago.
这倒是能解释是什么东西
Well, that explains all the people
在这八天里吃了那些人
who got eaten in the last eight days.
对
Yeah.
但问题是  他是怎么了
Question is, what happened to him?
迪恩
Dean.
你怎么想的
Uh, so, what do you think?
我不操这个的心
I'm not that worried about it.
什么意思
Excuse me?
挺奇怪的  是吧
That's funny, right?
我真他妈的不在乎
I could give two shakes of a rat's ass.
这么说对吗
Is that right?
他妈不在乎还是他不在乎
Do rats shake their ass, or is it something else?
把这个给我
Give me that.
为什么啊
Whoa, whoa! Why?!
这鬼三明治里放的什么鬼鸡肉啊
There's some funky chicken in the TDK slammer, ain't there?
对
Yeah.
这太傻了
This is stupid.
这不是我三明治惹的祸
My sandwich didn't do anything.
我不知道你们认为你们能找到什么
I don't know what you think you're gonna find.
你有点不正常啊  迪恩
There's something wrong with you, Dean.
你开什么玩笑  我没事
Are you kidding? I'm fine!
其实我感觉还是很不错的
I -- I actually feel great.
这是几个月来我感觉最好的一次
The best I've felt in a couple months.
小卡的事  黑色的胶状物
Cass? Black goo?
我现在都不在乎了
I don't even care anymore.
而且更妙的是
And you know what's even better?
那就是我不介意我这种不在乎
I don't care that I don't care.
我只想把我的三明治拿回来
I just want my damn slammer back.
伙计  你完全是嗑大了的样
Dude, you are completely stoned,
跟那个里克护林员一样
just like Ranger Rick was.
就像比格森餐厅里那些埋头大吃的人
Just like the dinner rush back at Biggerson's,
大家都爱死了火鸡鸭肉三明治
and everybody's loving the turducken.
我想你把我的三明治惹火了
I think you pissed off my sandwich.
我体内有那东西吗
That -- that's in me?
只有一半
O-only half of it.
这鼻涕状的东西看上去挺眼熟啊
Does that snot look familiar?
不管是什么把杰里·勃劳德变成了南瓜头
Okay, so whatever turned Gerry Browder into a pumpkin head...
它正在把迪恩变成一个大傻瓜
and is currently turning Dean into an idiot --
我还在这呢  就在这
I'm right here. Right here.
而它就在比格森餐厅的火鸡鸭三明治里吗
Is in the turducken slammer at Biggerson's.
-对  -在肉里
- Yeah. - It's in the meat.
如果现在我不是这么冷静  我肯定会吐
If I wasn't so chilled out right now, I would puke.
(比格森餐厅)
他怎么样了
How's he doing?
他在把二劲睡过去
He's sleeping it off.
撑得昏睡不醒了
Tryptophan coma.
你认为他会没事吗
So, you think he's okay?
对  他没事的
Yeah, he's all right.
好的
Good.
这么说你不担心他吗
So you don't worry about him?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
是说在他吃那三明治之前吗
Before the turducken?
对  我其实是想说
Yeah. Yeah, I kind of mean more like, uh...
在我崩溃之后...
more like ever since my head broke...
之后我们失去了小卡
and we lost Cass.
你有没有感觉到他...
I mean, you ever feel like he's --
他虽然举止没有什么变化
he's going through the same motions
但他不是原来那个迪恩了  你知道吗
but he's not the same Dean, you know?
他怎么能不变呢
How could he be?
对  但是如果...
Right, yeah, but what if --
如果什么  萨姆
what if - what, Sam?
你很担心他
You know, you worry about him.
他也很担心你
All he does is worry about you.
那你们俩还剩谁能正常过日子呢
Who's left to live their own life here?
你们俩...
The two of you --
你们俩这辈子斗妖魔鬼怪
aren't you full up just playing snuffleupagus
还不够烦的吗
with the devil all the live long?
我不知道  鲍比
I don't know, Bobby.
我倒无所谓老能看见路西法
Seeing Lucifer's fine with me.
再说一遍
Come again?
我不是说那挺有意思
Look, I'm not saying it's fun.
但跟你说实话
I mean, to be honest with you,
我把它当成最好的情况了
I kind of see it as the best-case scenario.
我是说
I mean...
至少我的疯狂还在一定范围之内  懂吗
at least all my crazy's under one umbrella, you know?
我大概知道我面对的是什么
I kind of know what I'm dealing with.
有很多人比我还惨
A lot of people got it worse.
你一直是一个很有内涵的混蛋
You always were one deep little son of a bitch.
慢着  慢着
Wait, wait, wait.
来了
Here we go.
我想我们得跟上他
Well, I guess we follow him.
(中西部肉食及家禽集散中心)
这真奇怪  对吗
That's weird, right?
像比格森餐厅这样的全国连锁店
I mean, national franchise like Biggerson's
会从一个像
getting meat from a place
假货批发市场似的地方进肉吗
that looks like it wholesales Hong Kong knockoffs.
好  对  是有点奇怪
Okay. Yeah. It's a little weird.
好吧
All right, well,
我想我们等到他们关店门
I guess we wait till they close up shop.
然后去四周看看
Go take a look around?
等等
Hang on.
不是吧
No.
是埃德加
Edgar.
是利维坦
Leviathans.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
这到底怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
有劳把他和其他人放在一起
Put him with the others, if you don't mind.
埃德加  跟我来
Edgar. Follow me.
我一直忙着实验
I've been so busy with this experiment.
都不知道你已经回来了
I didn't even realize you were back.
这挺重要的
It's, uh, big stuff.
我就是因为这个试验才回来的
I'm back because of the experiment.
怎么回事
What's happening?
你说你在改良配方
You said you were refining the formula.
没错  的确是的  现在进展十分好
Yes. Absolutely. And it's going great.
浓度降低  但吸收速率升高了
The absorption rate is up in lower concentrations.
但还是没有解决副作用的问题
But it didn't solve our little issue with adverse reactions.
是没有
Well, no.
没完全解决
Not 100%.
烧死他们
Burn them.
什么
What?
但他们反映了重要的试验数据
But they represent crucial test data.
添加剂配方哪里出了问题
Where the additive formula went wrong,
我的初步估测哪里失败了
where my initial projections failed.
迪克要来了
Dick is coming.
烧死他们
Burn them.
这里什么事都没有
There's nothing happening back here at all.
好吧  萨姆
Yeah, okay, Sam.
他们还在埋头苦干呢
Well, they're pretty dug in,
你转一圈四处看看就回来吧
so why don't you finish circling and head on back?
你的头怎么样了
How's your head?
我觉得那个三明治已经消耗得差不多了
Well, I think the slammer's pretty much wore off.
那之后我喝了二十杯咖啡
In between that and the 20 cups of coffee,
现在精神的很
I'm nicely tense and alarmed.
我没说那个
I wasn't talking about that.
鲍比  别
Oh, Bobby, don't --
别现在来给我心理分析  好吗
don't go all Sigmund Freud on me right now, okay?
我才刚被一个三明治下药了
I just got drugged by a sandwich.
我想谈谈你的新党派路线
I want to talk about your new party line.
党派
Party?
你在说什么  我甚至都不投票
What are you talking about? I don't even vote.
"这世界就是要自杀
"The world's a suicide case.
我们拯救了它  它转头就又要寻死了"
We save it, it just steals more pills"?
鲍比  我在这里  我在办这件案子
Bobby, I'm here, okay? I'm on the case.
有什么问题呢
What's the problem?
我目睹了许多猎魔人的生生死死
I've seen a lot of hunters live and die.
你说话开始像那些死人的了  迪恩
You're starting to talk like one of the dead ones, Dean.
不  我讲话就是一个正常人
No, I'm talking the way a person talks
已经承受太多  却不明白
when they've had it, when they can't figure out
当初自己为何会认为这些事很重要
why they used to think all this mattered.
你这个可怜可悲的...
Oh, you poor, sorry...
你不是个正常人
You're not a person.
真谢谢了
Thanks.
拜托
Come on, now.
你试过不再猎魔
You tried to hang it up
跟莉莎还有本过正常人的生活
and be a person with Lisa and Ben.
而现在你还是在这里
And now here you are
跟一个刻薄的老笨蛋待在装满了枪的车里
with a mean old coot and a van full of guns.
孩子  这可不是正常人会做的事
That ain't person behavior, son.
你就是个猎魔人
You're a hunter,
就是说你在干什么活儿就是什么人
meaning you're whatever the job you're doing today.
你要是变成了安妮·塞克斯顿(自白派代表诗人)
Now, you get a case of the Anne Sexton's,
总会有什么东西偷袭你
Something's gonna come up behind you
然后让你身首异处
and rip your fool head off.
现在  你给我找到振作起来的理由
Now, you find your reasons to get back in the game.
我才不管是爱是恨  抑或一个十元的赌
I don't care if it's love or spite or a $10 bet.
我已经参加过够多葬礼了  我认真的
I've been to enough funerals. I mean it.
你敢死在我前面  我就杀了你
You die before me, and I'll kill you.
我们得凑点钱
We need to scrape some money together,
给你弄个公寓什么的
get you a condo or something.
有情况了
Hey. Something's up.
这个世界太疯狂了
Well, I'll be a squirrel in a skirt.
是他妈的迪克·罗曼
It's Dick frigging Roman.
谁是他妈的迪克·罗曼
Who the hell is dick frigging roman?
亿万富翁迪克·罗曼
Billionaire Dick Roman,
出席近日的一个新闻发布会
seen here at a recent press conference,
在过去几个月中
has been on the corporate-takeover warpath
一直忙于吞并对头公司
in the last several months
丝毫没有心慈手软
and shows no signs of relenting.
我相信以前的好的美国价值观
I believe in good old American values,
比如说永无止境的发展
like unlimited growth.
但正如我一直说的那样
But it's like I always say --
如果你要赢  你就得是佼佼者
if you want to win, then you got to be the shark.
而大鱼吃小鱼
And a shark's got to eat.
这是个很好的问题
Well, that's a great question.
我们近来是吞并了几家公司
Yes, we have made new acquisitions.
我不靠恶意收购
I don't believe in hostile takeovers.
我靠的是兼并  然后反客为主
I believe in merging... and coming out on top.
不论是掌舵他赢得美国杯的快艇
Whether at the helm of his America's Cup-Winning Yacht
还是他的《财富》500强公司
or one of his Fortune 500 companies,
罗曼一直都是焦点人物
Roman has never shied away from the spotlight.
罗曼破纪录系列励志研讨会文集
Roman's record-breaking series of motivational seminars,
《入乡随俗》销量
"When in Rome," have outsold
已远超市场上的其他致富类项目
every other money-making program on the market.
他是全国步枪协会合唱团团员
A vocal member of the NRA
也是第二修正案坚定的拥护者
And a steadfast supporter of the Second Amendment,
罗曼也开始吸引
Roman has started attracting
一些保守派政客的注意
some conservative political attention, as well.
罗曼很冷酷  但他长得好
Roman is ruthless, but good-looking.
我认为他会成为一个很好的候选人
I think he'll make a great candidate.
又是一个好问题
Another great question.
不  我现在不会为政治职务竞选
No, I am not running for political office at this time.
但我的确有排名第一的畅销书
But I do have a number-one bestseller.
我勒个去
Holy crap.
这算什么
What the hell is that?
这是美国前50名
That's one of the top 50
最具影响力的人之一  迪恩
most powerful men in America, Dean.
自上个月起排名第35
Says here top 35 as of last month.
这就对了
Now it's all making sense.
还记得克劳力一直抱怨说讨厌迪克吗
Remember when Crowley kept going on about hating Dick?
我以为他是泛指呢
I thought he was just being general.
如果利维坦找上了他
Well, if the Leviathan got to him,
那就意味着他们的计划比我们想象的
then that means they're playing on a much bigger board
要大得多
than we were thinking.
那怎么办  我们不可能以火力取胜
So what, then? I mean, we can't exactly outgun them.
不行  但我们可以先发制人
No, but we got the drop on them.
我们还有个机会能搞清楚
Means we got a chance to figure out
这些人究竟在这里干什么
what these guys are really doing here.
你怎么弄到那货的
Whoa. Where'd you get that mother?
从弗兰克的监控设备大全里借的
It's on loan from Frank's big brother collection.
它能感应到半英里外的窗玻璃上的音频振动
It'll pick up vocal vibrations from window glass at half a mile.
是时候查清楚
Well, it's time to find out
这些恶心的混蛋在搞什么了
what these ugly bastards are up to.
病人被全身麻醉了
The patient is put under general anesthesia.
眼睛被固定住了
The eye is immobilized,
然后用手术刀分离视神经
Then a scalpel is used to sever the optic nerve.
我放入火鸭鸡三明治里的
The food additive that I've introduced
食物添加剂几乎百分百的有效
into the turducken has a near-100% rate of effectiveness.
一旦实验对象吃了
Once the subject tries it,
他们在几个小时内就会想要更多
they crave more within a few hours.
首剂就能作用于其DNA
With the very first dose, it starts to work on their DNA,
减慢他们的新陈代谢  导致体重增加
slowing their metabolism, causing weight gain,
还能抑制他们的情感波动
and dampening their emotional range,
让他们洋洋自得
which makes them perfectly complacent.
正如你所见
As you can see,
他们还没注意到奶奶已经过世了
They have yet to notice that Grandma is no longer with us.
的确  如果做好的肉饼
True, if you leave out a cooked patty
一小时后还没下肚
for more than an hour,
他们就会恢复成  怎么说
it reverts back to a somewhat, uh,
不太诱人的状态
unappealing state,
但目前还没人剩饭呢
but I have yet to have a case of leftovers.
你知道我喜欢什么吗
You know what I love?
除了手球和清新的夏敦埃酒
I mean, besides handball and a really crisp Chardonnay.
我就喜欢进步
I love progress.
我知道进步来源于合作
And I know that progress comes from collaboration,
所以此时此刻才特别激动人心
Which is what makes moments like this so thrilling.
我很高兴能听到这些
I am so glad to hear you say that.
那现在你能说说关于你失败的事吗
Now, what can you tell me about your failures?
什么
Hmm? My...
那些个流窜出去的
The ones that went off the rails
他们可是吃了你做的美餐
after they ate your little treats.
他们
I, um... They're, uh...
-失败是成功之母  -错
- They've been very instructive. - No.
我要让他们满足
See, I asked for complacency.
而不是自大
Not complacency
更不是那0.03%亢奋的食人者
and a 0.03% margin of hyperadrenalized cannibalism.
我会处理好这些的
I will have this under control.
惊现人肉煎饼  露营热季降温
"Camping high season harshed by human burrito"?
我之前是不是说过
Have I ever mentioned how I feel
我对我们的大业上报纸是什么态度
about our little forays making the papers?
再说一次  合作
But, again, collaboration.
进步
Progress.
我想把这次的错误
I want to turn this little mistake
变为一次极佳的教育机会
into a big fat teachable moment.
你愿意帮我吗
Will you help me with that?
好的
Well...Yes.
当然
Of course.
我们这边没动静  鲍比
Our side's still dead, Bobby.
你那边怎么样
Anything with you?
我也是
Same here.
等等
I got -- hold on.
有动静了  我这边  二楼
Yeah, I got movement -- my side, second floor,
会议室
meeting room.
我会重新安排
And I'll reschedule
跟议员在周二中午会餐
with the senator for lunch Tuesday.
你们可以在下午商讨大主教管区的事务
You can deal with the archdiocese in the afternoon.
很好
Fine.
迪克  听我解释
Dick, please, let me explain to you
我们的项目能提供什么
what our program has to offer.
不  让我告诉你为什么要关闭你的项目
No. Let me explain why we're shutting your program down.
关闭项目  这不行
We're shutting it down? No, you can't --
我关闭它是因为一条黄金法则
I'm shutting it down because of the one golden rule.
你知道吗
Do you know it?
知道  "不要让事情见报"
Yes. "Don't make the papers."
我保证
And I promise that --
不  黄金法则是
No, the golden rule is
世界上没有怪物
there's no such thing as monsters.
任何闹鬼闹怪的事
Anything stirs their little pots to the contrary --
都对我们的计划非常不利
very bad for our plans.
那么  我们怎么用你的错误
So, how can I use your mistake
教育你那些同事们呢
to communicate this to all your coworkers?
先生  我愿意做任何事
Listen, sir, I will do anything.
付出一切来弥补
I will give anything to make this right.
我知道你会的
I know you will.
你们要我自噬吗
You're bibbing me?
你知道你能给我们什么吗  医生
Do you know what you can give us, doctor?
杀鸡儆猴的教训
Your example.
发生什么了
What's happening now?
等等
Wait.
医生
Now, doc.
是时候了
It's time.
现在我算是什么都见识过了
Now I have officially seen it all.
鲍比  怎么了
Bobby, what is it?
他们让医生吃掉了他自己
He's making the doctor eat himself.
什么
What?
他
He's --
他们抓到他了
They got him.
迪恩  那儿至少有四个利维坦
Dean, there are at least four leviathans out there.
我们连一个都弄不死
We don't even know how to kill one.
要是我们就从正门进去
Well, it'll be quite a shock
一定吓掉他们大牙  是吧
when we walk in through the front door, won't it?
喷气机在奥黑尔待命
We'll have the jet on standby at O'hare.
周二早上
Thursday morning,
你要完成格里森的土地征用交易
you close on the land acquisition in Gleason.
好的
Fine.
而这是下午刚到的
And this came this afternoon.
在苏富比买的
Sotheby's.
太棒了
Outstanding!
谢谢你  苏珊
Thank you, Susan.
等等  苏珊
Oh, and, Susan?
那东西
Uh, tuh-tuh.
不  你没被绑起来  何必多此一举
No, you're not tied up. Why waste the effort?
我们都清楚你是逃不出我手心的
We both know that you're not gonna get past me.
你头还痛吗
How's your head?
你们抓到了迪克·罗曼
So you got Dick Roman.
我们要谁都行
We can have whoever we want.
比如说  我们要你也行
We could have you, for example.
前提是你得值得我们费这事
If you were worth the effort.
这话真伤人
Oh, you're hurting my feelings.
这个世界就是如此残酷  鲍比
Well, it's a hard world, Bob.
是我们吃狗的社会
It's an us-eat-dog world.
那是什么
What do you got there?
拍卖会上赢来的
Winning bid at auction.
真漂亮
Beautiful.
以无与伦比的准头闻名
Known for their peerless sighting.
我想你是爱枪之人吧
I imagine you appreciate guns.
现在有把我肯定爱
I'd appreciate one right about now.
不过我是泛指  枪的发明
But I mean the machine, the idea.
你们人类最富有创造力的一项发明之一
Just one of your species' most inspired inventions.
说真的  我真觉得人类很聪明
I mean it. I really think you guys have spunk.
你们的星球
You're like a planet
就像装着最可爱的小引擎
of just the cutest little engines that could.
但是
But...
正如前不久刚刚去世的真正的迪克·罗曼
Like the late, great, actual Dick Roman used to say
对他赶出总统套房的那个妓女所说的那样
to the whores he'd kick out of the presidential suite...
再可爱也不行啊  甜心
...Cute don't quite hack it, sugar.
咱们少废话了
Oh, let's just cut to the chase.
我显然不该多活这么长时间
I clearly ain't worth the extra time I'm getting here.
我要吃了你  鲍比
I'm gonna eat you, Bob.
没错
Yes.
但我希望我的饭做好准备
But I like my meals prepared.
再说了  留着你还有好处
Besides, holding on to you could pay big dividends.
我敢说你的朋友正赶来英雄救美呢
I bet your friends are on their way to rescue the damsel.
他们可聪明的很
Nah, they're too smart.
他们知道你们人多
They know they don't have the numbers.
来就是找死
It'd be suicide.
我也潇洒过了  还可能死得更惨呢
I've run my race. Could die worse.
(强力清洁剂)
呆在这儿别动
I'd stay in the chair.
好吧  狗娘养的
Okay, sons of bitches.
看看你们到底想干嘛
See what you're up to now.
我就拿走了
You're coming with me.
萨姆
Sam...
这可不是好好谈话的方式
That is not how we communicate from a place of yes.
这感觉真爽
That was bracing.
你们在哪儿找的这玩意儿
Where'd you kids find this stuff?
那是我的
That's mine.
快走
Go! Go!
你就不能别用那东西泼我吗
Would you stop it with that stuff?
见鬼  鲍比呢
Damn it, where's Bobby?
鲍比  快
Bobby! Come on!
快  快
Come on! Come on!
快走
Go! Go!
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
还好你进来了
I'm glad you got in.
他差点就爆了你的头
He almost took your freaking head off.
鲍比  给你帽子
Hey, Bobby, your hat.
鲍比
Bobby?
天啊  鲍比
Oh, god. Bobby?!
鲍比
Bobby?!